Hoosier State Press Association mss. 1969-1984 LMC 2717
Lilly Library
Hoosier State Press Association mss.
1969-1984
Lilly Library
Cardwell, Richard
LMC 2717
24 Boxes
The Hoosier State Press Association mss., 1933-1984, consist of background materials for the HSPA, as well as drafts of legislation by HSPA general counsel Richard Cardwell and issues of public debate.
Access Restrictions
This collection is open for research.
Many collections are housed offsite; retrieval requires advance notice. Please make an appointment a minimum of one week in advance of your visit.
Administrative History
The Hoosier State Press Association mss., ca. 1933-1984, was created by Richard W. Cardwell, General Counsel for the Hoosier State Press Association for twenty-five years.
The Hoosier State Press Association, founded in 1933, is a trade association that provides legal help, lobbying, and networking to Indiana newspapers.
Richard Cardwell, graduate of Kokomo High School (1951) and Indiana University (BA, 1955; JD, 1958), became HSPA general counsel in 1961. He was the primary author of the Indiana Open Door Law, which requires that the public have access to government meetings, and the Indiana Access to Public Records Act, which mandates that the public be allowed access to government records. He has represented the newspaper industry before the Indiana General Assembly on a number of First Amendment causes.
Scope and Content Note
The collection consists of background materials for the HSPA, as well as Cardwell drafts of the following legislation and issues of public debate: Open Committees in the General Assembly, 1969-1971; Juvenile Code, 1969-1979-; Open Door Law, 1975-1977; Public Record Law, 1976-1983; Governor's Commission on Individual Privacy, 1976-1977; Obscenity, 1974-1975; and Access to Criminal Proceedings, 1981-1982. In addition, the collection includes clippings, articles, and the association's files on legal developments affecting Indiana newspapers in thirty categories of operations.
Subject Files contain correspondence, memoranda, notes, legal documents, newspaper and magazine clippings, and government documents. Open Door Law contains correspondence, memoranda, notes, legal documents, clippings from newspapers and magazines, and government documents regarding House Bill 1022 & Senate Bill 83, House Bill 1237, Senate Bill 304, House Enrolled Act no. 1516, and Senate Enrolled Act no. 83, all of which concern public meetings. (These are also commonly referred to as "Sunshine Laws," "Sunshine Bills," "Open Records Laws," and "Open Meeting Laws.") Juvenile Code Records contain correspondence, memoranda, notes, legal documents, clippings from newspapers and magazines, and government documents. Freedom of Information Records contain correspondence, memoranda, notes, legal documents, clippings from newspapers and magazines, and government documents. Current Case Files contain correspondence, memoranda, notes, legal documents, clippings from newspapers and magazines, and government documents. Some subjects in Current Case Files overlap with Subject Files. The last series, Miscellaneous Files, contains various correspondence, memoranda, notes, legal documents, clippings from newspapers and magazines, and government documents unrelated to any previous series.
Arrangement
The collection is organized into the following series: I. Subject Files; II. Open Door Law Records; III. Juvenile Code Records; IV. Freedom of Information Records; V. Current Case Files; VI. Miscellaneous.
Acquisition Information
Acquired: 2003
Journalism --Societies, etc.; Journalism, Legal.; Freedom of the press.; Legislation --Indiana --20th century.; Indiana --Politics and government.; Indiana University; Journalism; Law; Hoosier State Press Association.
- Subject Files, 1933–1973; 1950s and early 1960s (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Organized alphabetically by subject, some of which are further subdivided by topic. Dates range from 1933–1973, with the bulk in the 1950s and early 1960s.
  - Advertising (General). Advertising Contracts, 1944-1968 (Box 1)
  - Advertising (General). Anniversary Issue, Planning of, 1957-1967 (Box 1)
  - Advertising (General). Anti-Price Advertising Laws, 1944-1966 (Box 1)
  - Advertising (General). Bankrupt (Going Out of Business) Sales, 1962 (Box 1)
  - Advertising (General). Budget Percentages, 1961-1964 (Box 1)
  - Advertising (General). Clairvoyant and Fortune-telling, 1961 (Box 1)
  - Advertising (General). Evaluation of Cost to Produce, 1961-1963 (Box 1)
  - Advertising (General). False Advertising, 1956-1962 (Box 1)
  - Advertising (General). Federal Trade Commission, 1947-1962 (Box 1)
  - Advertising (General). Firearms, 1961-1962 (Box 1)
  - Advertising (General). Free Advertising (Marking of, Postal Regulations), 1953-1960 (Box 1)
  - Advertising (General). Government Contractors Federal, 1961 (Box 1)
  - Advertising (General). Investment Advisors Federal, 1961 (Box 1)
  - Advertising (General). Not a Contract, 1960 (Box 1)
  - Advertising (General). Nursing Homes, 1960 (Box 1)
  - Advertising (General). Order in writing, 1949 (Box 1)
  - Advertising (General). Parking Meters, 1951-1963 (Box 1)
  - Advertising (General). Political Advertising (Marking of and Ban on Soliciting), 1946-1964 (Box 1)
  - Advertising (General). Price-fixing Laws, 1946-1957 (Box 1)
  - Advertising (General). Restrictions on Generally and in Other States, 1952-1963 (Box 1)
  - Advertising (General). Restrictive Ordinances Telephone Solicitation, 1958 (Box 1)
  - Advertising (General). Right of Ownership Copy, 1958 (Box 1)
  - Advertising (General). Right to Advertise Law, 1959-1962 (Box 1)
  - Advertising (General). Right to Censor Copy, 1948-1964 (Box 1)
  - Advertising (General). Right to Refuse or Reject, 1944-1965 (Box 1)
  - Advertising (General). Robinson-Patman Act, 1941-1946 (Box 1)
  - Advertising (General). Study for Exposure to National Newspaper Advertising, c., 1964 (Box 1)
  - Advertising (General). Tax, Deductibility of, 1955-1959 (Box 1)
  - Advertising (General). Unfair Competition, 1954 (Box 1)
  - Advertising (General). Unfair Competition Combination or Unit Advertising Structures Brief, 1950-1963 (Box 1)
  - Advertising (General). Use of Flat, 1960-1963 (Box 1)
  - Advertising (General). Use of Money Pictures of Prohibited, 1959-1970 (Box 1)
  - Advertising (General). Used Bedding Ads, 1958 (Box 1)
  - Advertising (General). Used Car Advertising, 1956 (Box 1)
  - Appraisers, 1943-1964 (Box 1)
  - Ballot Printing, 1944 (Box 1)
  - Ban on Magazine Distribution, 1948 (Box 1)
  - Better Business Bureau, 1964-1968 (Box 1)
  - Bonus Payments, 1947-1952 (Box 1)
  - Central Publishing, 1961-1969; (3 folders) (Box 1)
  - Child Labor, 1937-1946 (Box 1)
  - Circulation. General File, 1945-1962 (Box 1)
  - Circulation. Misrepresentation of, 1945-1965 (Box 1)
  - Comic Book Ordinances, 1955 (Box 1)
  - Compilation, Public Notice Laws of Indiana, Undated (Box 1)
  - Contempt of Court. Newspapers, 1942-1961 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence with Newspapers, 1957-1973 (Box 1)
  - Depreciation: Equipment, 1949-1968 (Box 1)
  - Equipment, Evaluation of, 1948-1961 (Box 1)
  - False Information to Newspapers, 1946-1964 (Box 1)
  - Freedom of the Press, 1942-1963 (Box 1)
  - Independent Contractors. General File, 1947-1963 (Box 2)
  - Inserts, 1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - Inserts. Supplements, 1948-1972; (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Labor Relations, 1961-1968; (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Labor Relations. American Newspaper Guild, 1944 (Box 2)
  - Labor Relations. Labor Relations Board, 1954 (Box 2)
  - Labor Relations. Right to Work and Agency Shop, Clauses, 1961-1964 (Box 2)
  - Labor Relations. Taft-Hartley Act, 1947-1962 (Box 2)
  - Laws and Legislation (National), 1943-1952 (Box 2)
  - Laws and Legislation (State), 1947-1961 (Box 2)
  - Legal Advertising, 1963-1967 (Box 2)
  - Legal Advertising. Annual School Report, 1963-1965 (Box 2)
  - Legal Advertising. Assessment of Real Estate Notice, 1941 (Box 2)
  - Legal Advertising. Birth Notice Publication, 1943 (Box 2)
  - Legal Advertising. Budget and Tax Levy Notice, 1944-1965 (Box 2)
  - Legal Advertising. Change of Name or Publication Site, 1939-1965 (Box 2)
  - Legal Advertising. Claim Form for Publishers, 1957-1960 (Box 2)
  - Legal Advertising. Claims & Allowances, 1963 (Box 2)
  - Legal Advertising. Circulation as Basis, 1939-1950 (Box 2)
  - Legal Advertising. Construction of Term - "Newspaper" - Political Affiliation - Free Circulation, 1933-1969 (Box 2)
  - Legal Advertising. Court Decisions, Etc., 1943-1966 (Box 2)
  - Legal Advertising. Duties of Officials, 1940-1953 (Box 2)
  - Legal Advertising. Election Notices (empty) (Box 2)
  - Legal Advertising. Five Year Clause, 1933-1966 (Box 2)
  - Legal Advertising. Highway Department Notices, 1950 (Box 2)
  - Legal Advertising. Library Annual Report, 1942-1946 (Box 2)
  - Legal Advertising. Newspapers - Definition - Right to Publish Leg. Advertising, 1957-1959 (Box 2)
  - Legal Advertising. Notice to Quiet Title, 1946 (Box 2)
  - Legal Advertising. Price of Publication, 1946-1964 (Box 2)
  - Legal Advertising. Publication of Penalty Ordinances, 1953-1965 (Box 2)
  - Legal Advertising. Rates, 1943-1963 (Box 2)
  - Legal Advertising. Suspension of Paper, 1963 (Box 2)
  - Legal Advertising. TWP Trustee Annual Report - New Law -, 1951; 1951-1954 (Box 2)
  - Liability of Employer for Employee, 1948 (Box 2)
  - Libel, 1940-1964; (3 folders) (Box 2)
  - Licensing of Newspapers, 1942-1961 (Box 2)
  - Lotteries, 1943-1968; (3 folders) (Box 2)
  - Misrepresentation. Liability, 1953 (Box 2)
  - Monopolies, 1949 (Box 2)
  - National Newspaperboy Day. Governor's Proclamation, 1965 (Box 3)
  - N.E.A. Bulletins., 1961-1962 (Box 3)
  - Newspaper Cases., 1938-1960 (Box 3)
  - Newspaper Institute of America., 1951-1960 (Box 3)
  - Newspaper Public Information Committee., 1964-1967 (Box 3)
  - Newspaper. Management, 1951-1967; (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Newspapers. General Circulation, Undated (Box 3)
  - News Pictures., 1946-1947 (Box 3)
  - Nuisance Newspapers., Undated (Box 3)
  - Offset., 1961-1969 (Box 3)
  - Optometry Publicity., 1949-1965; (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Ordinances., 1940-1966 (Box 3)
  - Paper, History of., 1962 (Box 3)
  - Pension and Profit Sharing Plan., 1949-1968 (Box 3)
  - Photography., 1951-1963 (Box 3)
  - Plant Layout., 1962 (Box 3)
  - Pleadings, Contents of (Privilege)., 1947-1954 (Box 3)
  - Postal Laws and Regulations., 1939-1966; (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Postal Sectional Centers. Comments on by Members, 1965-1967 (Box 3)
  - Public Records, Inspection of., 1948-1968; (3 folders) (Box 3)
  - Public Relations Brochures and Newspaper Promotion., 1943-1966 (Box 3)
  - Publishing in Case of Disaster., 1957-1963 (Box 3)
  - Questionable Concerns., 1951-1969 (Box 3)
  - Questionable Concerns (continued)., 1951-1969 (Box 4)
  - Radio. General File, 1943-1948 (Box 4)
  - Readability of Newspapers., 1947 (Box 4)
  - Robinson-Patman Act., 1936-1937 (Box 4)
  - Rural Correspondents, Independent Contractors. (Dearborn Pub. Col. & Winemac Repub.), 1939-1967; (2 folders) (Box 4)
  - Sales Tax. Adjusted Gross Income Tax, 1960-1964 (Box 4)
  - Sales Tax. Dept. of Revenue Releases, Forms, etc., 1963-1965 (Box 4)
  - Sales Tax. General Information, 1963 (Box 4)
  - Sales Tax. Industry Guidelines, 1963 (Box 4)
  - Sales Tax. Newspapers. Sales Tax Returns, 1963 (Box 4)
  - Sales Tax. Research, 1960-1963 (Box 4)
  - Sales Tax. Sales Tax Meeting, 1963 (Box 4)
  - Sample Copies., 1951 (Box 4)
  - Saturday Promotion., 1955 (Box 4)
  - Selective Service and G. I. Bill., 1944-1951 (Box 4)
  - Severance Pay Policies., Undated (Box 4)
  - Sick Leave Policies on Pay., 1953-1957 (Box 4)
  - Social Security. Coverage, 1951-1957 (Box 4)
  - Social Security. Federalization, 195? (Box 4)
  - Social Security. Old Age Benefits, 1939-1968 (Box 4)
  - Social Security. Records Inspection, 1939 (Box 4)
  - Social Security. Unemployment Comp., 1940-1951 (Box 4)
  - State & Federal Govt. Offices Dealing with Personnel Relations. Received Oct., 1950, 1950? (Box 4)
  - Suburban Newspapers., 1961 (Box 4)
  - Syndicated Features., 1963-1973 (Box 4)
  - Taxation. Corporations., 1949-1962 (Box 4)
  - Taxation. State Property., 1956-1967; (3 folders) (Box 4)
  - Taxation of Advertising., 1963-1969 (Box 4)
  - Taxes. Federal, 1946-1967 (Box 5)
  - Taxes. Federal Withholding, 1943 (Box 5)
  - Taxes. Gross Income, 1933-1948 (Box 5)
  - Taxes. Illinois Rental Tax, 1961-1964 (Box 5)
  - Taxes. License Taxes, 1964-1969 (Box 5)
  - Tax on Advertising. Iowa., 1967-1970 (Box 5)
  - Textbooks., 1950 (Box 5)
  - Trademarks., 1946-1965 (Box 5)
  - Typography., 1962-1967 (Box 5)
  - Unemployment Compensation. Law and Matters, 1957-1966 (Box 5)
  - Unfair Competition., 1960-1963 (Box 5)
  - Unfair Competition and Violation of Copyright., 1955-1964 (Box 5)
  - Veterans. Administration., 1948-1953 (Box 5)
  - Veterans. General File., 1945 (Box 5)
  - Wage-Hour Law., 1943-1970; (5 folders) (Box 5)
  - Wage-Hour Law. Amendments, 1947-1963 (Box 5)
  - Wage-Hour Law. Correspondence, 1941-1955 (Box 5)
  - Wage-Hour Law. Court & Administrative Rulings, etc., 1938-1963 (Box 5)
  - Wage-Hour Law. Definitions & Coverage, 1939-1963 (Box 5)
  - Wage-Hour Law. General File, 1958-1964 (Box 5)
  - Wage-Hour Law. Pertaining to Weeklies, 1939-1942 (Box 5)
  - Wage-Hour Law. "Printing", 1951 (Box 5)
  - Wage-Hour Law. Suggested Payroll Record Forms, 1939-1940 (Box 5)
  - Welfare. Public and Social Security, 1951 (Box 5)
  - Workmen's Compensation Insurance., 1936-1965 (Box 5)
- Open Door Law Records, 1966-1979 (Box 6)
  Dates range from 1966-1979.
  - 1977 - Access. H.B. 1022 & S.B. 83, HSPA "Open Door Law", 1976-1977 (Box 6)
  - Models., 1966-1979; (2 folders) (Box 6)
  - Revisions (1979). (Box 6)
  - Survey., 1978 (Box 6)
  - Task Force., 1975-1976 (Box 6)
  - Candidates' Responses., 1976 (Box 6)
  - Examples of Secrecy., 1975-1977; (2 folders) (Box 6)
  - H.B. 1237 1976. Legislative History, 1969-1977; (3 folders) (Box 6)
  - H.B. 1237 1976. Newspaper Articles Related to It, 1975-1976 (Box 6)
  - Interim Study Committee (1976)., 1973-1976; (3 folders) (Box 6)
- Juvenile Code Records, 1965-1979 (Box 6)
  Dates range from 1965-1979.
  - Federation of Clubs - Attitudes Toward Juvenile Court Publications. H.B. 1028., 1969; 1977 (Box 6)
  - H.B. 1028. Proposed Amendment, 1979 (Box 7)
  - House Enrolled Acts 2107., Undated (Box 7)
  - Indiana Juvenile Code., 1977 (Box 7)
  - Indiana Juvenile Code. Proposed Final Draft (September 1977) (Box 7)
  - Information About Juveniles - Indiana., 1965-1979; (2 folders) (Box 7)
  - Juvenile Records and Proceedings Access Survey, Replies., 1973 (Box 7)
  - Policies on Juveniles., 1964-1977 (Box 7)
  - Proposed Juvenile Code (1977-1978)., 1976-1978; (2 folders) (Box 7)
  - Rules of Juvenile Procedure. Supreme Court of Indiana., 1973-1974 (Box 7)
  - S.B. 15 - Access to Information (1969). (Box 7)
  - S.B. 15, S.B. 112, & H.B. 1028., 1969-1978; (2 folders) (Box 7)
  - S.B. 112. Access to Information (1971)., 1969-1971 (Box 7)
- Freedom of Information Records, 1954-1977 (Box 7)
  Dates range from 1954-1977.
  - Access to Police Records (1964-1974)., 1964-1976 (Box 7)
  - Access to Police Records (1975-1977). (Box 7)
  - Convention Legislative Speech (1969). (Box 7)
  - Freedom of Information Center., 1968-1975 (Box 7)
  - Freedom of Information Center. Advisory Committee Meetings (1963) (Box 7)
  - Freedom of Information Center. Advisory Council Meeting (1967) (Box 7)
  - Freedom of Information Center. Advisory Council Meeting (Feb, 27, 1970) (Box 7)
  - Freedom of Information Center. Advisory Council Memos, 1961-1970; (2 folders) (Box 8)
  - Freedom of Information Center. Conference (1966) (Box 8)
  - Freedom of Information Center. Consulting, 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Freedom of Information Center. Correspondence, 1963-1971 (Box 8)
  - Freedom of Information Center. General Materials, 1958-1969 (Box 8)
  - Freedom of Information Center. Information About, 1963-1972; (3 folders) (Box 8)
  - Freedom of Information Center. Information About Sustaining Members, 1963-1966 (Box 8)
  - Freedom of Information Center. Keeping the Press Free, 1963 (Box 8)
  - Freedom of Information Conference Speeches (1958-1961) (Box 8)
  - Freedom of Information Conference Speeches (1962-1964), 1962-1968 (Box 8)
  - Position Papers (1963-1965)., 1964-1965 (Box 8)
  - Position Papers (1966-1970). (Box 8)
  - Sigma Delta Chi Reports., 1954-1970 (Box 8)
- Current Case Files, 1941-1978; 1960s (Box 9)
  Arrangement
  Series is organized alphabetically by subject, some of which are further subdivided into topical divisions.
  Dates range from 1941-1978, with the bulk in the 1960s.
  - Advertising., 1963-1976; (5 folders) (Box 9)
  - Advertising. Terre Haute Ad Club Speech., May 21, 1969; 1967-1969 (Box 9)
  - Advertising. Unreported Cases. Recent Developments, 1961-1977; (8 folders) (Box 9)
  - Contempt of Court., 1963-1972; (2 folders) (Box 9)
  - Contempt of Court. Memphis (Tenn.) Contempt Cases, 1968 (Box 9)
  - Contempt of Court. Unreported Cases, Recent Developments, 1962-1977 (Box 9)
  - Copyright., 1963-1976; (2 folders) (Box 10)
  - Copyright. Unreported Cases - Recent Developments, 1963-1977 (Box 10)
  - During-Trial Publicity., 1962-1975; (6 folders) (Box 10)
  - During-Trial Publicity. Post Shepard, 1966-1976; (2 folders) (Box 10)
  - During-Trial Publicity. Unreported Cases - Recent Developments, 1975-1977; (2 folders) (Box 10)
  - Federal Communications Commission., 1963-1972; (2 folders) (Box 10)
  - Federal Communications Commission. Unreported Cases - Recent Developments, 1964-1977 (Box 10)
  - Federal Court Jurisdiction., 1963-1970 (Box 10)
  - Federal Court Jurisdiction. Unreported Cases - Recent Developments, 1967-1977 (Box 10)
  - Federal Trade Commission., 1963-1968 (Box 10)
  - Federal Trade Commission. Unreported Cases - Recent Developments, 1964-1976 (Box 10)
  - Freedom of Press., 1962-1977; (16 folders) (Box 11)
  - Freedom of Press. Unreported Cases - Recent Developments, 1963-1969; (4 folders) (Box 12)
  - Free Press - Fair Trial. American Newspaper Publishers Association Report, 1966-1967; (2 folders) (Box 12)
  - Free Press - Fair Trial. Hearings, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Free Press - Fair Trial. Medina Report. Association of the Bar of the City of New York, 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Free Press - Fair Trial. Reardon Report & Comments, 1964-1969; (7 folders) (Box 12)
  - Free Press - Fair Trial. Restrictions on News Coverage by Courts, 1969-1972 (Box 12)
  - Free Press - Fair Trial. Restrictions on News Coverage by Courts. Pre-Trial, 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Free Press - Fair Trial. Restrictions on News Coverage by Courts. During Trial, 1966-1968 (Box 12)
  - Free Press - Fair Trial. Restrictions on News Coverage by Courts. Post-Trial, 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Free Press - Fair Trial. Restrictions on News Release by Police. Pre-Trial, 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Independent Contractors (Carrier Boys - Mail Route Carrier)., 1962-1974 (Box 13)
  - Independent Contractors. Unreported Cases - Recent Developments, 1964-1977; (2 folders) (Box 13)
  - Labor Relations., 1964-1976; (4 folders) (Box 13)
  - Labor Relations. Unreported Cases - Recent Developments, 1964-1977; (7 folders) (Box 13)
  - Legal Advertising and Notice., 1963-1969; (5 folders) (Box 14)
  - Legal Advertising and Notice. Unreported Cases - Recent Developments, 1964-1977; (5 folders) (Box 14)
  - Libel., 1962-1976; (7 folders) (Box 14)
  - Libel (continued)-, 1963-1967; (5 folders) (Box 15)
  - Libel. Unreported Cases - Recent Developments, 1962-1977; (5 folders) (Box 15)
  - Libel After NY Times., 1964-1971; (7 folders) (Box 15)
  - Libel After NY Times., 1964-1966 (Box 16)
  - Libel After NY Times. Unreported Cases - Recent Developments, 1964-1968; (2 folders) (Box 16)
  - Libel (Cases #301- )., 1964-1969; (5 folders) (Box 16)
  - Lotteries., 1964-1975 (Box 16)
  - Lotteries. Unreported Cases - Recent Developments, 1964-1977 (Box 16)
  - Newsman's Privilege. Federal Free Flow of Information Act, 1972-1973; (3 folders) (Box 16)
  - Newsman's Privilege. National Conference of Commissioners on Uniform State Laws, 1970 (Box 16)
  - Newspapers. General, 1964-1970 (Box 16)
  - Newspapers. General. Unreported Cases - Recent Developments, 1970-1974; (2 folders) (Box 16)
  - Obscenity., 1961-1976; (10 folders) (Box 17)
  - Obscenity. Unreported Cases - Recent Developments, 1965-1974 (Box 17)
  - Open Meetings. Unreported Cases - Recent Developments, 1965-1977; (5 folders) (Box 17)
  - Open Meetings. Unreported Cases - Recent Developments (continued), 1969-1975; (4 folders) (Box 18)
  - Photography in Courtrooms., 1963-1976 (Box 18)
  - Photography in Courtrooms. Unreported Cases - Recent Developments, 1959-1978; (2 folders) (Box 18)
  - Post Office., 1963-1974 (Box 18)
  - Post Office. Unreported Cases - Recent Developments, 1964-1977; (6 folders) (Box 18)
  - Prejudicial Publicity. Codes of Cooperation, 1962-1968; (2 folders) (Box 19)
  - Prejudicial Publicity. Court Cases, 1960-1967; (2 folders) (Box 19)
  - Prejudicial Publicity. Law Enforcement Changes, 1963-1967; (2 folders) (Box 19)
  - Prejudicial Publicity. Seminars and Panels, 1964-1967; (2 folders) (Box 19)
  - Prejudicial Publicity. Speeches and Comment, 1963-1968; (5 folders) (Box 19)
  - Prejudicial Publicity. Statutory Proposals, 1961-1967 (Box 19)
  - Prejudicial Publicity. Studies, 1953-1968; (2 folders) (Box 19)
  - Pre-trial Publicity., 1963-1966; (6 folders) (Box 20)
  - Pre-trial Publicity. Post Sheppard, 1966-1976; (7 folders) (Box 20)
  - Pre-trial Publicity. Unreported Cases - Recent Developments, 1961-1969; (2 folders) (Box 20)
  - Professional Immunity Law, 1963-1977; (3 folders) (Box 21)
  - Professional Immunity Law. Unreported Cases - Recent Developments, 1962-1977; (6 folders) (Box 21)
  - Professional Status Law for Reporters, 1949-1967 (Box 21)
  - Protection of News Source Case. Philadelphia Bulletin, 1963 (Box 21)
  - Public Records., 1963-1977; (3 folders) (Box 21)
  - Public Records. Unreported Cases - Recent Developments, 1964-1977; (3 folders) (Box 21)
  - Right of Privacy., 1941-1977; (6 folders) (Box 22)
  - Right of Privacy. Unreported Cases. Recent Developments, 1961-1977; (4 folders) (Box 22)
  - Taxes., 1963-1974 (Box 22)
  - Taxes. Unreported Cases - Recent Developments, 1964-1977; (5 folders) (Box 22)
  - Trade Names and Unfair Competition, 1963-1976; (3 folders) (Box 23)
  - Trade Names and Unfair Competition. Unreported Cases - Recent Developments, 1965-1974 (Box 23)
  - Wage-Hour Law., 1963-1974; (2 folders) (Box 23)
  - Wage-Hour Law. Unreported Cases - Recent Developments, 1964-1978; (2 folders) (Box 23)
- Miscellaneous Files, 1964-1980; 1975 (Box 23)
  Organized alphabetically by subject.
  Dates range from 1964-1980, with the bulk in 1975.
  - 1975 Independent Magazine Distributors of Indiana (Obscenity Legislation)., 1974-1975; (2 folders) (Box 23)
  - 1975 Legislature - State Campaign Financing and Election Reform Law., 1974 (Box 23)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Advertising (Price Fixing)., 1975-1980 (Box 23)
  - Attorney Advertising., 1975-1978; (2 folders) (Box 23)
  - Banks vs. Holder., 1973; (2 folders) (Box 23)
  - Banks vs. Holder. Court of Appeals, Seventh Circuit, 1973; (2 folders) (Box 24)
  - Clippings., 1975-1981; (2 folders) (Box 24)
  - Current Cases., 1964 (Box 24)
  - "Display" Ordinances - Marion and Munice., 1974-1975 (Box 24)
  - Federal and State Energy Conservation and Rationing Plans (1979-80)., 1979-1980 (Box 24)
  - Hustler and Indiana Obscenity Law., 1977 (Box 24)
  - Indiana Periodicals Distributors Assn. - 1974 General Assembly. (Box 24)
  - Legal Decisions - Ginsberg, Miller, Heller, Jenkins, CineCom., 1967-1973 (Box 24)
  - Obscenity Legislation (Magazine Distributors Assn.)., 1973-1974 (Box 24)
  - Responses on Police Records Withholding., 1974-1976 (Box 24)